<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Resources About Piracy by Ultimate Tower Builders</title>
    <link>http://ultimatetowerbuilders.me/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Resources About Piracy by Ultimate Tower Builders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2016 13:40:00 +1100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://ultimatetowerbuilders.me/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Articles</title>
      <link>http://ultimatetowerbuilders.me/post/articles/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2016 13:40:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ultimatetowerbuilders.me/post/articles/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Articles chosen by Ultimate Tower Builders about the topic of piracy in the modern world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;erfan&#34;&gt;Erfan&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;the-helpfulness-of-copyright-misuse-in-dmca-circumvention-http-search-proquest-com-ezproxy-lib-monash-edu-au-docview-1728267897-abstract-9a1d1d4577504974pq-1-accountid-12528&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://search.proquest.com.ezproxy.lib.monash.edu.au/docview/1728267897/abstract/9A1D1D4577504974PQ/1?accountid=12528&#34;&gt;THE HELPFULNESS OF COPYRIGHT MISUSE IN DMCA CIRCUMVENTION&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The article written in 2014 by Lauren Stewart, explores the freedom that DMCA has granted copyright holders to implement anticircumvention protection on their software beyond what it was originally intended. It uses the MDY v. Blizzard case as a case study for this kind of abuse. Moreover copyright holders are hindering new legislation about DMCA by lobbying against it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;aiden&#34;&gt;Aiden&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;julian&#34;&gt;Julian&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;can-the-madness-be-monetized-an-exploratory-survey-of-music-piracy-and-acquisition-behaviour-http-search-lib-monash-edu-primo-library-libweb-action-display-do-tabs-detailstab-ct-display-fn-search-doc-tn-gale-ofa243453518-indx-7-recids-tn-gale-ofa243453518-recidxs-6-elementid-6-rendermode-poppedout-displaymode-full-frbrversion-8-frbg-dscnt-0-scp-scps-scope-28catelec-29-scope-28catau-29-scope-28mua-29-scope-28catcarm-29-scope-28mulo-29-plug-peepopenrimo-central-multiple-fe-vid-mon-mode-basic-srt-rank-tab-default-tab-dum-true-vl-28freetext0-29-piracy-20music-dstmp-1475984455945&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://search.lib.monash.edu/primo_library/libweb/action/display.do?tabs=detailsTab&amp;amp;ct=display&amp;amp;fn=search&amp;amp;doc=TN_gale_ofa243453518&amp;amp;indx=7&amp;amp;recIds=TN_gale_ofa243453518&amp;amp;recIdxs=6&amp;amp;elementId=6&amp;amp;renderMode=poppedOut&amp;amp;displayMode=full&amp;amp;frbrVersion=8&amp;amp;frbg=&amp;amp;&amp;amp;dscnt=0&amp;amp;scp.scps=scope:%28catelec%29,scope:%28catau%29,scope:%28MUA%29,scope:%28catcarm%29,scope:%28mulo%29&amp;lt;Plug&amp;gt;PeepOpenrimo_central_multiple_fe&amp;amp;vid=MON&amp;amp;mode=Basic&amp;amp;srt=rank&amp;amp;tab=default_tab&amp;amp;dum=true&amp;amp;vl%28freeText0%29=piracy%20music&amp;amp;dstmp=1475984455945&#34;&gt;Can the madness be monetized? An exploratory survey of music piracy and acquisition behaviour&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Written by Storm Gloor and Clyde Philip Rolston, this 2010 article looks at digital piracy in the music industry and more specifically, why people pirate music and how it effects the industry. This is a good article as it presents some interesting ideas regarding the philosophy behind piracy, focusing more on why people do it, and suggests possible solutions/outcomes based
on adapting to how people think instead of punishing them. The findings are based off a survey that asks &amp;ldquo;why non-payers acquired tracks without paying&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;Tracks downloaded per month&amp;rdquo;, and suggested pricing for music, among other things. The survey results are included in the article and provide information from several demographics. The article was part of the annual peer reviewed MEIEA (music and entertainment industry educators association) journal, which is made up of educators
and academics in the music and entertainment industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;christopher&#34;&gt;Christopher&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;james&#34;&gt;James&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;software-piracy-in-research-a-moral-analysis-http-search-proquest-com-ezproxy-lib-monash-edu-au-docview-1695135184-fulltextpdf-f304a428e91541d2pq-1-accountid-12528&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://search.proquest.com.ezproxy.lib.monash.edu.au/docview/1695135184/fulltextPDF/F304A428E91541D2PQ/1?accountid=12528&#34;&gt;Software Piracy in Research: A Moral Analysis&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Software Piracy in Research: A Moral Analysis&lt;/strong&gt; was an article written by Gary Santillanes and Ryan Marshall Felder and published in August 2015 to ‘Science and Engineering Ethics’ issue 21.4 page 967-977, a journal discussing ethical issues faced by modern scientists and engineers. This article discusses the need that modern researchers have for advanced software to conduct concise and effective research and addresses the fact that not all researchers can afford the software they need. Many researchers who believe their work enhance the quality of human life are often found in an
ethical dilemma deciding if they should break the law and pirate software that they could otherwise not afford or simply restrict their research to what can be completed with the free software that is available. This article argues that many scientists moral code drives them to seriously consider the illegal piracy of such software in order continue their pursuit in valuable research.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Books</title>
      <link>http://ultimatetowerbuilders.me/post/books/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2016 13:40:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ultimatetowerbuilders.me/post/books/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Books chosen by Ultimate Tower Builders about the topic of piracy in the modern world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;erfan&#34;&gt;Erfan&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;handbook-on-the-economics-of-copyright-http-www-elgaronline-com-ezproxy-lib-monash-edu-au-view-9781849808521-xml&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.elgaronline.com.ezproxy.lib.monash.edu.au/view/9781849808521.xml&#34;&gt;Handbook on the Economics of Copyright&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Featuring expert contributors from around the world, this book offers insight into the vital theoretical and practical aspects of the economics of copyright. Topics discussed include fair use, performers’ rights, copyright and trade, online music streaming, internet piracy, copyright and visual art markets, and open source publishing. In addition to in-depth coverage of these timely topics, the authors also offer insightful predictions and policy recommendations for the future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;aiden&#34;&gt;Aiden&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;julian&#34;&gt;Julian&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;piracy-of-digital-content-http-search-lib-monash-edu-primo-library-libweb-action-display-do-tabs-detailstab-ct-display-fn-search-doc-catau51246149780001751-indx-5-recids-catau51246149780001751-recidxs-4-elementid-4-rendermode-poppedout-displaymode-full-frbrversion-rfngrpcounter-1-vl-2841902380ui0-29-any-query-any-contains-plug-peepopeniracy-dscnt-0-search-scope-au-everything-scp-scps-scope-28catelec-29-scope-28catau-29-scope-28mua-29-scope-28catcarm-29-scope-28mulo-29-plug-peepopenrimo-central-multiple-fe-fctv-books-mode-basic-vid-mon-institution-mua-rfngrp-1-tab-default-tab-fctn-facet-rtype-fromdl-vl-28freetext0-29-piracy-dstmp-1475902346644&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://search.lib.monash.edu/primo_library/libweb/action/display.do?tabs=detailsTab&amp;amp;ct=display&amp;amp;fn=search&amp;amp;doc=catau51246149780001751&amp;amp;indx=5&amp;amp;recIds=catau51246149780001751&amp;amp;recIdxs=4&amp;amp;elementId=4&amp;amp;renderMode=poppedOut&amp;amp;displayMode=full&amp;amp;frbrVersion=&amp;amp;rfnGrpCounter=1&amp;amp;vl%2841902380UI0%29=any&amp;amp;query=any,contains&amp;lt;Plug&amp;gt;PeepOpeniracy&amp;amp;dscnt=0&amp;amp;search_scope=au_everything&amp;amp;scp.scps=scope:%28catelec%29,scope:%28catau%29,scope:%28MUA%29,scope:%28catcarm%29,scope:%28mulo%29&amp;lt;Plug&amp;gt;PeepOpenrimo_central_multiple_fe&amp;amp;fctV=books&amp;amp;mode=Basic&amp;amp;vid=MON&amp;amp;institution=MUA&amp;amp;rfnGrp=1&amp;amp;tab=default_tab&amp;amp;fctN=facet_rtype&amp;amp;fromDL=&amp;amp;vl%28freeText0%29=piracy&amp;amp;dstmp=1475902346644&#34;&gt;Piracy of Digital Content&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Written by Piotr Stryszowski and Danny Scorpecci, This book was published on the 7th of July 2009 and was done as part of a project by OECD; a multinational organisation that focuses on economics and world trade, in order to give a greater understanding of digital piracy and raise awareness of the effects caused by intellectual property infringements. There are only 134 pages with 3 main chapters, a case study and 3 annexes, so it is fairly
easy to read through and provides a good insight and overview of the issue of digital piracy. The first chapter looks at the different markets and industries that piracy effects (such as music, movies, software, books, etc.) and looks at how and why these industries suffer from piracy by looking at their economic properties. Chapter 2 looks at piracy as its own market, exploring factors like the supply/demand of digital piracy and what drives it. The third chapter
discusses the actions industries have taken to try and combat digital piracy and the final chapter (case study), looks at the sports sector and how broadcasting, streaming, and dvd releases are effected by piracy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;christopher&#34;&gt;Christopher&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;james&#34;&gt;James&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;software-piracy-exposed-http-www-sciencedirect-com-ezproxy-lib-monash-edu-au-science-book-9781932266986&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.sciencedirect.com.ezproxy.lib.monash.edu.au/science/book/9781932266986&#34;&gt;Software Piracy Exposed&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Software Piracy Exposed&lt;/strong&gt; is a book written by Paul Craig, Ron Honick and Mark Burnett and published in 2005. This book discusses the reality of software piracy and the serious repercussions that are caused by both private and corporate software piracy that takes place. From the birth of software piracy in the 1980’s this book goes into detail describing the evolution of how software is pirated and the reality that these pirates have damaged the software industry. The process undertaken by pirates is reviewed in this
book, beginning with getting access to the software, cracking any copy protection technology that has been used to protect against piracy and then distributing the software (usually over the internet through complex distribution chains). The authors emphasize that these pirates partaking in organized crime and are incredibly skilled at what they do. As it currently stands the authors suggest that piracy cannot simply be stopped, these are incredible smart people who find great pleasure in
cracking these “undefeatable” software locks. In conclusion the authors suggest that the only hope to stop piracy is in the evolution of “copy protection technology’s” that cannot be broken by pirates.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>