<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Resources About Piracy by Ultimate Tower Builders</title>
    <link>http://ultimatetowerbuilders.me/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Resources About Piracy by Ultimate Tower Builders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2016 13:40:00 +1100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://ultimatetowerbuilders.me/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Articles</title>
      <link>http://ultimatetowerbuilders.me/post/articles/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2016 13:40:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ultimatetowerbuilders.me/post/articles/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Articles chosen by Ultimate Tower Builders about the topic of piracy in the modern world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;erfan&#34;&gt;Erfan&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;the-helpfulness-of-copyright-misuse-in-dmca-circumvention-http-search-proquest-com-ezproxy-lib-monash-edu-au-docview-1728267897-abstract-9a1d1d4577504974pq-1-accountid-12528&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://search.proquest.com.ezproxy.lib.monash.edu.au/docview/1728267897/abstract/9A1D1D4577504974PQ/1?accountid=12528&#34;&gt;THE HELPFULNESS OF COPYRIGHT MISUSE IN DMCA CIRCUMVENTION&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The article written in 2014 by Lauren Stewart, explores the freedom that DMCA has granted copyright holders to implement anticircumvention protection on their software beyond what it was originally intended. It uses the MDY v. Blizzard case as a case study for this kind of abuse. Moreover copyright holders are hindering new legislation about DMCA by lobbying against it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;aiden&#34;&gt;Aiden&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;piracy-in-the-digital-age-university-of-california-san-diego-http-courses-cs-washington-edu-courses-csep590-06au-projects-digital-piracy-pdf&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://courses.cs.washington.edu/courses/csep590/06au/projects/digital-piracy.pdf&#34;&gt;Piracy in the Digital Age - University of California, San Diego&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The peer-reviewed article titled ‘Piracy in the Digital Age’ was written by the following five authors: Dana Dashstrom, Nathan Farrington, Daniel Gobera, Ryan Roemer, and Nabil Schear. IT was published by the University of California in San Diego in 2006. This article focusses on the digital side of piracy. The article beings by introducing piracy by explaining the technical background and motivation and consequences for pirating. It continues by talking about the history behind piracy. It begins by talking about the history when piracy first come about then continues by talking about piracy in the 20th century then concludes by talking about recent history. The author continues by talking more in depth about software piracy and its origins. Further, they then discuss the technical parts behind software piracy including, open and close source programs as well as software locks. Following that, they discuss the legalities behind this piracy and provides some legal battles that have occurred due to these laws. The last topic they cover is the Digital Millennium Copyright Act and stopping the lock pickers. Finally, concludes the article by summarising the main points. The authors leave the reader thinking about how fast digital piracy is accelerating and that more problems are going to arise due to this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;julian&#34;&gt;Julian&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;can-the-madness-be-monetized-an-exploratory-survey-of-music-piracy-and-acquisition-behaviour-http-search-lib-monash-edu-primo-library-libweb-action-display-do-tabs-detailstab-ct-display-fn-search-doc-tn-gale-ofa243453518-indx-7-recids-tn-gale-ofa243453518-recidxs-6-elementid-6-rendermode-poppedout-displaymode-full-frbrversion-8-frbg-dscnt-0-scp-scps-scope-28catelec-29-scope-28catau-29-scope-28mua-29-scope-28catcarm-29-scope-28mulo-29-plug-peepopenrimo-central-multiple-fe-vid-mon-mode-basic-srt-rank-tab-default-tab-dum-true-vl-28freetext0-29-piracy-20music-dstmp-1475984455945&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://search.lib.monash.edu/primo_library/libweb/action/display.do?tabs=detailsTab&amp;amp;ct=display&amp;amp;fn=search&amp;amp;doc=TN_gale_ofa243453518&amp;amp;indx=7&amp;amp;recIds=TN_gale_ofa243453518&amp;amp;recIdxs=6&amp;amp;elementId=6&amp;amp;renderMode=poppedOut&amp;amp;displayMode=full&amp;amp;frbrVersion=8&amp;amp;frbg=&amp;amp;&amp;amp;dscnt=0&amp;amp;scp.scps=scope:%28catelec%29,scope:%28catau%29,scope:%28MUA%29,scope:%28catcarm%29,scope:%28mulo%29&amp;lt;Plug&amp;gt;PeepOpenrimo_central_multiple_fe&amp;amp;vid=MON&amp;amp;mode=Basic&amp;amp;srt=rank&amp;amp;tab=default_tab&amp;amp;dum=true&amp;amp;vl%28freeText0%29=piracy%20music&amp;amp;dstmp=1475984455945&#34;&gt;Can the madness be monetized? An exploratory survey of music piracy and acquisition behaviour&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Written by Storm Gloor and Clyde Philip Rolston, this 2010 article looks at digital piracy in the music industry and more specifically, why people pirate music and how it effects the industry. This is a good article as it presents some interesting ideas regarding the philosophy behind piracy, focusing more on why people do it, and suggests possible solutions/outcomes based on adapting to how people think instead of punishing them. The findings are based off a survey that asks &amp;ldquo;why non-payers acquired tracks without paying&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;Tracks downloaded per month&amp;rdquo;, and suggested pricing for music, among other things. The survey results are included in the article and provide information from several demographics. The article was part of the annual peer reviewed MEIEA (music and entertainment industry educators association) journal, which is made up of educators and academics in the music and entertainment industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;christopher&#34;&gt;Christopher&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;music-piracy-and-the-audio-home-recording-act-https-dltr-law-duke-edu-2002-11-20-music-piracy-and-the-audio-home-recording-act&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dltr.law.duke.edu/2002/11/20/music-piracy-and-the-audio-home-recording-act/&#34;&gt;Music Piracy and the Audio Home Recording Act&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The peer reviewed article by Tia Hall discusses the effect of piracy on the music industry and the approaches companies have taken against the acts of piracy which are harming the industry. Tia showcases the facts of in which some “Major Music Labels develop Anti-Piracy Technology” with examples of Sony’s developed anti-piracy technology used against Piracy. Showing how the music industry is affected and how society responds to it through anti-piracy measures being taken by digital content owners and the United States legislature to combat piracy and evaluate them in light of the AHRA.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;james&#34;&gt;James&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;software-piracy-in-research-a-moral-analysis-http-search-proquest-com-ezproxy-lib-monash-edu-au-docview-1695135184-fulltextpdf-f304a428e91541d2pq-1-accountid-12528&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://search.proquest.com.ezproxy.lib.monash.edu.au/docview/1695135184/fulltextPDF/F304A428E91541D2PQ/1?accountid=12528&#34;&gt;Software Piracy in Research: A Moral Analysis&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Software Piracy in Research: A Moral Analysis&lt;/strong&gt; was an article written by Gary Santillanes and Ryan Marshall Felder and published in August 2015 to ‘Science and Engineering Ethics’ issue 21.4 page 967-977, a journal discussing ethical issues faced by modern scientists and engineers. This article discusses the need that modern researchers have for advanced software to conduct concise and effective research and addresses the fact that not all researchers can afford the software they need. Many researchers who believe their work enhance the quality of human life are often found in an ethical dilemma deciding if they should break the law and pirate software that they could otherwise not afford or simply restrict their research to what can be completed with the free software that is available. This article argues that many scientists moral code drives them to seriously consider the illegal piracy of such software in order continue their pursuit in valuable research.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Books</title>
      <link>http://ultimatetowerbuilders.me/post/books/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2016 13:40:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ultimatetowerbuilders.me/post/books/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Books chosen by Ultimate Tower Builders about the topic of piracy in the modern world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;erfan&#34;&gt;Erfan&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;handbook-on-the-economics-of-copyright-http-www-elgaronline-com-ezproxy-lib-monash-edu-au-view-9781849808521-xml&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.elgaronline.com.ezproxy.lib.monash.edu.au/view/9781849808521.xml&#34;&gt;Handbook on the Economics of Copyright&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This book explores the world of copyright from an economist&amp;rsquo;s point of view. Featuring many experts in the field, they explore different area of copyright including legal structure of copyright, public domain, licensing, piracy and economical impact of all of those. This book explores both the legal and economical aspects of copyright, and therefore is especially suitable for students studying copyright and its impacts in depth. Published in 2014, this book explores recent developments in the issue of copyright, which is very important as the rise of P2P networks (e.g. BitTorrent) and has introduced new challenges for copyright holders.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;aiden&#34;&gt;Aiden&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;steal-this-computer-book-4-0-http-search-lib-monash-edu-primo-library-libweb-action-display-do-jsessionid-2682d18b471abe57581d82c18792fd1a-tabs-detailstab-ct-display-fn-search-doc-catau21188873860001751-indx-1-recids-catau21188873860001751-recidxs-0-elementid-0-rendermode-poppedout-displaymode-full-frbrversion-vl-41902380ui0-any-query-any-2ccontains-2csteal-this-book-4-0-dscnt-0-search-scope-au-everything-scp-scps-scope-3a-28catelec-29-2cscope-3a-28catau-29-2cscope-3a-28mua-29-2cscope-3a-28catcarm-29-2cscope-3a-28mulo-29-2cprimo-central-multiple-fe-vid-mon-highlight-true-institution-mua-bulksize-10-tab-default-tab-displayfield-title-dym-true-vl-freetext0-steal-20this-20book-204-0-query2-steal-this-book-4-0-dstmp-1476235714295&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://search.lib.monash.edu/primo_library/libweb/action/display.do;jsessionid=2682D18B471ABE57581D82C18792FD1A?tabs=detailsTab&amp;amp;ct=display&amp;amp;fn=search&amp;amp;doc=catau21188873860001751&amp;amp;indx=1&amp;amp;recIds=catau21188873860001751&amp;amp;recIdxs=0&amp;amp;elementId=0&amp;amp;renderMode=poppedOut&amp;amp;displayMode=full&amp;amp;frbrVersion=&amp;amp;vl(41902380UI0)=any&amp;amp;query=any%2Ccontains%2CsteAL+THIS+BOOK+4.0&amp;amp;dscnt=0&amp;amp;search_scope=au_everything&amp;amp;scp.scps=scope%3A%28catelec%29%2Cscope%3A%28catau%29%2Cscope%3A%28MUA%29%2Cscope%3A%28catcarm%29%2Cscope%3A%28mulo%29%2Cprimo_central_multiple_fe&amp;amp;vid=MON&amp;amp;highlight=true&amp;amp;institution=MUA&amp;amp;bulkSize=10&amp;amp;tab=default_tab&amp;amp;displayField=title&amp;amp;dym=true&amp;amp;vl(freeText0)=steAL%20THIS%20BOOK%204.0&amp;amp;query2=steAL+THIS+BOOK+4.0&amp;amp;dstmp=1476235714295&#34;&gt;Steal this computer book 4.0&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The peer-reviewed article titled ‘Piracy in the Digital Age’ was written by the following five authors: Dana Dashstrom, Nathan Farrington, Daniel Gobera, Ryan Roemer, and Nabil Schear. IT was published by the University of California in San Diego in 2006. This article focusses on the digital side of piracy. The article beings by introducing piracy by explaining the technical background and motivation and consequences for pirating. It continues by talking about the history behind piracy. It begins by talking about the history when piracy first come about then continues by talking about piracy in the 20th century then concludes by talking about recent history. The author continues by talking more in depth about software piracy and its origins. Further, they then discuss the technical parts behind software piracy including, open and close source programs as well as software locks. Following that, they discuss the legalities behind this piracy and provides some legal battles that have occurred due to these laws. The last topic they cover is the Digital Millennium Copyright Act and stopping the lock pickers. Finally, concludes the article by summarising the main points. The authors leave the reader thinking about how fast digital piracy is accelerating and that more problems are going to arise due to this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;julian&#34;&gt;Julian&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;piracy-of-digital-content-http-search-lib-monash-edu-primo-library-libweb-action-display-do-tabs-detailstab-ct-display-fn-search-doc-catau51246149780001751-indx-5-recids-catau51246149780001751-recidxs-4-elementid-4-rendermode-poppedout-displaymode-full-frbrversion-rfngrpcounter-1-vl-2841902380ui0-29-any-query-any-contains-plug-peepopeniracy-dscnt-0-search-scope-au-everything-scp-scps-scope-28catelec-29-scope-28catau-29-scope-28mua-29-scope-28catcarm-29-scope-28mulo-29-plug-peepopenrimo-central-multiple-fe-fctv-books-mode-basic-vid-mon-institution-mua-rfngrp-1-tab-default-tab-fctn-facet-rtype-fromdl-vl-28freetext0-29-piracy-dstmp-1475902346644&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://search.lib.monash.edu/primo_library/libweb/action/display.do?tabs=detailsTab&amp;amp;ct=display&amp;amp;fn=search&amp;amp;doc=catau51246149780001751&amp;amp;indx=5&amp;amp;recIds=catau51246149780001751&amp;amp;recIdxs=4&amp;amp;elementId=4&amp;amp;renderMode=poppedOut&amp;amp;displayMode=full&amp;amp;frbrVersion=&amp;amp;rfnGrpCounter=1&amp;amp;vl%2841902380UI0%29=any&amp;amp;query=any,contains&amp;lt;Plug&amp;gt;PeepOpeniracy&amp;amp;dscnt=0&amp;amp;search_scope=au_everything&amp;amp;scp.scps=scope:%28catelec%29,scope:%28catau%29,scope:%28MUA%29,scope:%28catcarm%29,scope:%28mulo%29&amp;lt;Plug&amp;gt;PeepOpenrimo_central_multiple_fe&amp;amp;fctV=books&amp;amp;mode=Basic&amp;amp;vid=MON&amp;amp;institution=MUA&amp;amp;rfnGrp=1&amp;amp;tab=default_tab&amp;amp;fctN=facet_rtype&amp;amp;fromDL=&amp;amp;vl%28freeText0%29=piracy&amp;amp;dstmp=1475902346644&#34;&gt;Piracy of Digital Content&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Written by Piotr Stryszowski and Danny Scorpecci, This book was published on the 7th of July 2009 and was done as part of a project by OECD; a multinational organisation that focuses on economics and world trade, in order to give a greater understanding of digital piracy and raise awareness of the effects caused by intellectual property infringements. There are only 134 pages with 3 main chapters, a case study and 3 annexes, so it is fairly easy to read through and provides a good insight and overview of the issue of digital piracy. The first chapter looks at the different markets and industries that piracy effects (such as music, movies, software, books, etc.) and looks at how and why these industries suffer from piracy by looking at their economic properties. Chapter 2 looks at piracy as its own market, exploring factors like the supply/demand of digital piracy and what drives it. The third chapter discusses the actions industries have taken to try and combat digital piracy and the final chapter (case study), looks at the sports sector and how broadcasting, streaming, and dvd releases are effected by piracy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;christopher&#34;&gt;Christopher&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;computer-ethics-a-case-based-approach-robert-n-barger-2008-http-search-lib-monash-edu-primo-library-libweb-action-display-do-tabs-detailstab-ct-display-fn-search-doc-catau21167566930001751-indx-1-recids-catau21167566930001751-recidxs-0-elementid-0-rendermode-poppedout-displaymode-full-frbrversion-frbg-dscnt-0-scp-scps-scope-3a-28catelec-29-2cscope-3a-28catau-29-2cscope-3a-28mua-29-2cscope-3a-28catcarm-29-2cscope-3a-28mulo-29-2cprimo-central-multiple-fe-vid-mon-mode-basic-srt-rank-tab-default-tab-dum-true-vl-freetext0-computer-20ethics-20-3a-20a-20case-based-20approach-2c-20robert-20n-20barger-2c-202008-dstmp-1476234635156&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://search.lib.monash.edu/primo_library/libweb/action/display.do?tabs=detailsTab&amp;amp;ct=display&amp;amp;fn=search&amp;amp;doc=catau21167566930001751&amp;amp;indx=1&amp;amp;recIds=catau21167566930001751&amp;amp;recIdxs=0&amp;amp;elementId=0&amp;amp;renderMode=poppedOut&amp;amp;displayMode=full&amp;amp;frbrVersion=&amp;amp;frbg=&amp;amp;&amp;amp;dscnt=0&amp;amp;scp.scps=scope%3A%28catelec%29%2Cscope%3A%28catau%29%2Cscope%3A%28MUA%29%2Cscope%3A%28catcarm%29%2Cscope%3A%28mulo%29%2Cprimo_central_multiple_fe&amp;amp;vid=MON&amp;amp;mode=Basic&amp;amp;srt=rank&amp;amp;tab=default_tab&amp;amp;dum=true&amp;amp;vl(freeText0)=Computer%20ethics%20%3A%20a%20case-based%20approach%2C%20Robert%20N.%20Barger%2C%202008&amp;amp;dstmp=1476234635156&#34;&gt;Computer ethics : a case-based approach, Robert N. Barger, 2008&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The resource Computer ethics: a case-based approach, discusses the many ethical practices that society has taken in many cases. The many principles surrounding ethical dilemmas involving digital media are examined through a philosophical view rather than a legal approach through Robert N. Barger. Twenty-nine cases are recorded in this book discussing the man real-life experiences of computer professionals to show the literal effects of computer ethics for students and those interested to learn and contribute to society.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;james&#34;&gt;James&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;software-piracy-exposed-http-www-sciencedirect-com-ezproxy-lib-monash-edu-au-science-book-9781932266986&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.sciencedirect.com.ezproxy.lib.monash.edu.au/science/book/9781932266986&#34;&gt;Software Piracy Exposed&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Software Piracy Exposed&lt;/strong&gt; is a book written by Paul Craig, Ron Honick and Mark Burnett and published in 2005. This book discusses the reality of software piracy and the serious repercussions that are caused by both private and corporate software piracy that takes place. From the birth of software piracy in the 1980’s this book goes into detail describing the evolution of how software is pirated and the reality that these pirates have damaged the software industry. The process undertaken by pirates is reviewed in this book, beginning with getting access to the software, cracking any copy protection technology that has been used to protect against piracy and then distributing the software (usually over the internet through complex distribution chains). The authors emphasize that these pirates partaking in organized crime and are incredibly skilled at what they do. As it currently stands the authors suggest that piracy cannot simply be stopped, these are incredible smart people who find great pleasure in cracking these “undefeatable” software locks. In conclusion the authors suggest that the only hope to stop piracy is in the evolution of “copy protection technology’s” that cannot be broken by pirates.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>