<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Piracy Resources</title>
    <link>http://ultimatetowerbuilders.me/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Piracy Resources</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2016 13:40:00 +1100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://ultimatetowerbuilders.me/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Articles</title>
      <link>http://ultimatetowerbuilders.me/post/articles/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2016 13:40:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ultimatetowerbuilders.me/post/articles/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;erfan&#34;&gt;Erfan&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;aiden&#34;&gt;Aiden&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;julian&#34;&gt;Julian&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Can the madness be monetized? An exploratory survey of music piracy and acquisition behaviour&lt;/strong&gt; Written by Storm Gloor and Clyde Philip Rolston, this 2010 article looks at digital piracy in the music industry and more specifically, why people pirate music and how it effects the industry. This is a good article as it presents some interesting ideas regarding the philosophy behind piracy, focusing more on why people do it, and suggests possible solutions/outcomes based
on adapting to how people think instead of punishing them. The findings are based off a survey that asks “why non-payers acquired tracks without paying”, “Tracks downloaded per month”, and suggested pricing for music, among other things. The survey results are included in the article and provide information from several demographics. The article was part of the annual peer reviewed MEIEA (music and entertainment industry educators association) journal, which is made up of educators
and academics in the music and entertainment industry. This article can be accessed throught the monash library system
&lt;a href=&#34;http://search.lib.monash.edu/primo_library/libweb/action/display.do?tabs=detailsTab&amp;amp;ct=display&amp;amp;fn=search&amp;amp;doc=TN_gale_ofa243453518&amp;amp;indx=7&amp;amp;recIds=TN_gale_ofa243453518&amp;amp;recIdxs=6&amp;amp;elementId=6&amp;amp;renderMode=poppedOut&amp;amp;displayMode=full&amp;amp;frbrVersion=8&amp;amp;frbg=&amp;amp;&amp;amp;dscnt=0&amp;amp;scp.scps=scope:%28catelec%29,scope:%28catau%29,scope:%28MUA%29,scope:%28catcarm%29,scope:%28mulo%29&amp;lt;Plug&amp;gt;PeepOpenrimo_central_multiple_fe&amp;amp;vid=MON&amp;amp;mode=Basic&amp;amp;srt=rank&amp;amp;tab=default_tab&amp;amp;dum=true&amp;amp;vl%28freeText0%29=piracy%20music&amp;amp;dstmp=1475984455945&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;christopher&#34;&gt;Christopher&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;james&#34;&gt;James&lt;/h1&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Books</title>
      <link>http://ultimatetowerbuilders.me/post/books/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2016 13:40:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ultimatetowerbuilders.me/post/books/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;erfan&#34;&gt;Erfan&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My resources&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;aiden&#34;&gt;Aiden&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;julian&#34;&gt;Julian&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Piracy of Digital Content&lt;/strong&gt; Written by Piotr Stryszowski and Danny Scorpecci, This book was published on the 7th of July 2009 and was done as part of a project by OECD; a multinational organisation that focuses on economics and world trade, in order to give a greater understanding of digital piracy and raise awareness of the effects caused by intellectual property infringements. There are only 134 pages with 3 main chapters, a case study and 3 annexes, so it is fairly
easy to read through and provides a good insight and overview of the issue of digital piracy. The first chapter looks at the different markets and industries that piracy effects (such as music, movies, software, books, etc.) and looks at how and why these industries suffer from piracy by looking at their economic properties. Chapter 2 looks at piracy as its own market, exploring factors like the supply/demand of digital piracy and what drives it. The third chapter
discusses the actions industries have taken to try and combat digital piracy and the final chapter (case study), looks at the sports sector and how broadcasting, streaming, and dvd releases are effected by piracy. This book can be accessed through monash library system
&lt;a href=&#34;http://search.lib.monash.edu/primo_library/libweb/action/display.do?tabs=detailsTab&amp;amp;ct=display&amp;amp;fn=search&amp;amp;doc=catau51246149780001751&amp;amp;indx=5&amp;amp;recIds=catau51246149780001751&amp;amp;recIdxs=4&amp;amp;elementId=4&amp;amp;renderMode=poppedOut&amp;amp;displayMode=full&amp;amp;frbrVersion=&amp;amp;rfnGrpCounter=1&amp;amp;vl%2841902380UI0%29=any&amp;amp;query=any,contains&amp;lt;Plug&amp;gt;PeepOpeniracy&amp;amp;dscnt=0&amp;amp;search_scope=au_everything&amp;amp;scp.scps=scope:%28catelec%29,scope:%28catau%29,scope:%28MUA%29,scope:%28catcarm%29,scope:%28mulo%29&amp;lt;Plug&amp;gt;PeepOpenrimo_central_multiple_fe&amp;amp;fctV=books&amp;amp;mode=Basic&amp;amp;vid=MON&amp;amp;institution=MUA&amp;amp;rfnGrp=1&amp;amp;tab=default_tab&amp;amp;fctN=facet_rtype&amp;amp;fromDL=&amp;amp;vl%28freeText0%29=piracy&amp;amp;dstmp=1475902346644&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;christopher&#34;&gt;Christopher&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;james&#34;&gt;James&lt;/h1&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>